Leaving...It's harder than you think
Exit is a horror film directed by Michael Fausti.
Events take a sinister turn one night in London, when two very
different couples arrive at a double-booked apartment.
Actions have consequences and not all debts are paid for with money.
Leaving, it's harder than you think.
Russell Bone, played by Tony Denham.
Man On the Phone, played by Michael Fausti.
Steve, played by Billy James Machin.
Adrienne, played by Charlotte Gould.
Moe, played by Robert Alexander.
Beaten Man, played by Ryan Hardy.
French Exit is a 2020 black comedy drama film directed by Azazel
Jacobs and adapted by Patrick deWitt from his 2018 novel.
It tells the story of a Manhattan heiress (Michelle Pfeiffer) who moves to Paris
with her son (Lucas Hedges) with the little money they have left.
The film had its world premiere at the New York Film Festival on October 10, 2020, and was
theatrically released in the United States and Canada on February 12, 2021.
It received mixed reviews from critics, although Pfeiffer's performance was praised and she was
nominated for the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy.
The film explores themes of haunted house, surreal,
surrealism, film noir, art house.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.